Gayatri Mayur Gaikwad

Address: Flat no.2201, Building no. 12-Elymus, Regency Anantam,

Vicco Naka, Kalyan-Shil Road, Dombivali East-421203.

Contact No.: (M) +91 9930695463

E-mail: salokhe_gayatri@yahoo.in



CAREER OBJECTIVE:

Seeking a position to utilize my skills and abilities for a company providing good working environment so that I can extract more knowledge and effectively contribute in progress of the company with my dedication towards work.

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

Total Work Experience: 14 years

Company/Organization	Designation	Duration
Oberoi International School, Mumbai	Sr. Accounts Executive	06 th Mar 2017 to till date
Sumil Chemical Industries Pvt. Ltd., Mumbai	Accounts Executive	18 th Jan 2011 to 04 th Mar 2017
Essel-World, Mumbai	Accountant	09 th Aug 2009 to 10th Jan 2011

WORK EXPERIENCE:

1. Presently working with Oberoi International School, Goregaon, Mumbai.

Designation: Sr. Accounts Executive

Duration: 06th Mar 2017 To till date (6 Years 4 Months as on 25th July 2023)

Notice Period: 2 Months

Responsibilities:

Process Invoices: Receive & review invoices, verifying accuracy, verify all purchase orders/work orders in terms of accounts payable, check GST related details GSTIN, HSN/SAC, GST rate etc. on invoices, Deduct TDS as applicable, completeness & proper authorization, Code invoices to appropriate general ledger accounts & cost centers. Processing employees monthly travelling expenses, mediclaim & other reimbursements. Check the entitlement for expense claims submitted.

Fixed Assets: Fixed assets invoice processing & payments making, assets creation, assets deletion, Yearly Fixed assets verification, and preparing reports such as FA register.

Payment Processing: Prepare & process payments including cheques, electronic transfers & wire transfers. Ensure timely & accurate payment of invoices while adhering to payment terms & internal policies.

Vendor Management: Maintain vendor records, communicate with vendors regarding payment inquiries & discrepancies & resolve any issues or disputes.

Expenses Reconciliation: Reconcile vendor statements & resolve discrepancies to ensure accurate accounts payable records.

Recordkeeping: Maintain organized and up-to-date accounts payable files and documentation including invoices, purchase orders and payment records.

Reporting: Prepare regular records on accounts payable activities, such as outstanding invoices, ageing analysis and Unmatched report, Open PO report.

Compliance: Ensure compliance with company policies, accounting principles and applicable laws & regulations. Monthly TDS, PF & PT payments.

Team Collaboration: Work collaboratively with other departments such as purchasing, finance and procurement to resolve issues and improve processes.

Other: Create vendor master for new suppliers & employees, verification of PAN & GST numbers of suppliers, making accounts related PO/WO, Passing GRN/service entry & Parking/posting invoices.

2. Sumil Chemical Industries Pvt. Ltd., Mumbai

Designation: Accounts Executive

Duration: 18th Jan 2011 to 04th Mar 2017 (6 Years 1 Month)

Responsibilities:

- To ensure day to day accounting, expenses bill booking.
- Ensure payments to Vendors, Payroll processing, Management Reports of the company in SAP.
- Ensuring the compliance of Various Statutory payments related to the company i.e. VAT, TDS, Service Tax etc.
- Bank Reconciliation & liaison with the banks for various daily purposes.
- Group Company's reconciliation, Branch related expenses & Non-CTC related expenses booking.
- Documentation & other requirements such as Form 15CB & 15CA related to foreign remittances.
- To participate in periodical finalization of the company's books & liaison with the auditors for the audit of the same.
- Interacting with statutory & internal auditors & to address their queries/requirements.
- Ensure the compliances with various time to time corporate guidelines.
- Compliance & analysis of creditors & their ageing.

3. Essel-World, Borivali, Mumbai

Designation: Accountant

Duration: 09th Aug 2009 to 10th Jan 2011 (1 Year 5 Months)

Responsibilities: To handle day to day accounting activities & Bank Reconciliation.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION:

Qualification	Passing Year	Grade	University
B. Com	2008	II Grade	Mumbai University
H.S.C.	2005	II Grade	Mumbai University
S.S.C.	2003	II Grade	Mumbai University

SOFTWARE PROFICIENCY:

- SAP Finance & Controlling
- Tally ERP 9
- MS Office 2013

CERTIFICATIONS:

• SAP FICO (Finance & Controlling)

PERSONAL SKILLS:

Good problem-solving ability, good verbal and written communication skills, sincerity, hard-working, ability to deal with people diplomatically, willingness for more knowledge, dedication towards work, completion of work within the stipulated time.

PERSONAL PROFILE:

• Date of Birth : 20th August 1987

Nationality : Indian
Marital Status : Married
Pan Card No. : CCDPS3403E

Hobbies : Reading, Listening MusicLanguages Known : English, Hindi and Maarthi

I, hereby declare that all the information mentioned above is correct and authentic as per my knowledge.

Gayatri Mayur Gaikwad